$ASIS_IncreasedSpawnPage	Increased Spawns
$ASIS_RandomSpawnPage	Spawn Randomizer
$ASIS_NPCPotionPage	NPC Potions
$ASIS_HeaderSpawnWeight	Spawn Weight
$ASIS_HeaderOptions	Options
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight0	Weighting to have NO Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight1	Spawn Weight for 1 Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight2	Spawn Weight for 2 Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight3	Spawn Weight for 3 Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight4	Spawn Weight for 4 Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight5	Spawn Weight for 5 Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight6	Spawn Weight for 6 Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight7	Spawn Weight for 7 Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight8	Spawn Weight for 8 Spawns
$ASIS_SliderSpawnWeight9	Spawn Weight for 9 Spawns
$ASIS_ToggleISReducedInterior	Reduced Interior Spawns
$ASIS_ToggleRSUseInterior	Use Interior Spawns
$ASIS_SliderRSRandomSpawnChance	Chance for Random Spawns
$ASIS_SliderRSMultiGroupChance	Chance for Multiple Groups
$ASIS_SliderNPCPotionItems	Number of Potions
$ASIS_SliderNPCPotionChance	Chance per Potion
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight0	This is the corresponding chance that no extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for no spawns. \nDefault: 200
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight1	This is the corresponding chance that 1 extra spawn will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 1 extra spawns. \nDefault: 150
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight2	This is the corresponding chance that 2 extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 2 extra spawns. \nDefault: 35
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight3	This is the corresponding chance that 3 extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 3 extra spawns. \nDefault: 10
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight4	This is the corresponding chance that 4 extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 4 extra spawns. \nDefault: 3
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight5	This is the corresponding chance that 5 extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 5 extra spawns. \nDefault: 2
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight6	This is the corresponding chance that 6 extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 6 extra spawns. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight7	This is the corresponding chance that 7 extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 7 extra spawns. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight8	This is the corresponding chance that 8 extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 8 extra spawns. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoISSpawnWeight9	This is the corresponding chance that 9 extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 9 extra spawns. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight0	This is the corresponding chance that no extra spawns will occur. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for no Spawns. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight1	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 1 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 1 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight2	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 2 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 2 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 50
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight3	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 3 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 3 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 25
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight4	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 4 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 4 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 15
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight5	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 5 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 5 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 3
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight6	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 6 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 6 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 1
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight7	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 7 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 7 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight8	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 8 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 8 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoRSSpawnWeight9	This is the corresponding chance that a group will have 9 spawn. \nThe higher the number, the higher the chance for 9 spawn in a group. \nDefault: 0
$ASIS_InfoSISReducedInterior	This setting determines if increased spawns are reduced indoors. \nDefault: Enabled
$ASIS_InfoRsRandomSpawnChance	This is the chance for a random group to spawn - it's per NPC, so watch when turned up. \nDefault: 3
$ASIS_InfoRSMultiGroupChance	This setting determines the chance for multiple groups to appear. \nDefault: 10
$ASIS_InfoRSUseInterior	This determines if the random group spawns can happen indoors. \nDefault: Disabled
$ASIS_InfoNPCPotionItems	This setting determines how many potions will be used in the potion chances. \nDefault: 5
$ASIS_InfoNPCPotionChance	This setting determines how likely it is a potion will be given to an NPC \nDefault: 10